{
    "id": "5ef458657d85415b928135579888c7be",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He sold the land …………………….. belonged to his brother.",
            "description": "Which is used to refer to things. That can also refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no horse …………………….. I can lend you.",
            "description": "That can refer to both people and things. It is more common than which after words like no, all, any etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The marks ………………………… were left by the whip were still visible.",
            "description": "Which is used to refer to things. That can also refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He died in the house ……………………….. he was born.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Those ………………………… are healthy do not need any physician.",
            "description": "Who refers to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were accosted by a young girl …………………………. was a tourist guide.",
            "description": "Who refers to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The camel ………………………… I bought from the merchant is old.",
            "description": "Which is used to refer to things. That can also refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t stand the stench ……………………….. comes from this drain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "who",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a man ………………………… was blind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I found the key ………………………… I had lost.",
            "description": "Which is used to refer to things. That can also refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A castle ………………………….. is built on a hill cannot be hid.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A man ………………………… is industrious is sure to succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}